# ABDERRAHIM NABAOUI

# UNITY GAME DEVELOPER

@ nabaoui.abderrahim@gmail.com +212637852855

Agadir, Morocco



# https://www.gamox.ma/portfolio

 Unity game programmer with over 8 years of experience in programming and problem solving, 5 years in web/mobile development, and 3 years in the gaming field. In 2020 I launched my start-up Gamox (Gamox.ma) to get in touch with other hyper-casual studios. and recently I worked with 9tales (9tales.io) to release their NFT demo card game.

# Experience

# **Unity Game Developer**

 www.9tales.io ₱ 9tales

- **2021 2022**
- Create 9tales demo NFT card game.
- Transform 100% of design specification into functional games.
- Implement some of the game 3D models and VFX.
- Communicate with other 3 team members.

#### Gamox CEO

■ Gamox 

**2020 - 2022** 

- Led my startup to create 4 hyper-casual mobile games in Unity 3D.
- Collaboration with Moonee studio publisher on 3 hyper-casual games, (Brain Master 3D, Stack Crowds Running 3D, Stack Crowds Running 3D)

# 1337 School Projects

**1337** 

# www.1337.ma

**2016 - 2018** 

- Make a small Ray tracing engine in C language, supporting mirror effect, transparency and texture in 3D space.
- Recreate Shadowmatic full game from scratch in unity 3D.

#### **Project Manager**

Fikralabs 

www.fikralabs.com 
2016 - 2018

- Developed the 1st platform web to announce used cars for sell.
- Designed 3 websites: Fikralabs, Hotel Targante, If-company.
- Developed Lqliaa Municipality website.

## Education

# Information Technology Architect (Computer Graphic)

1337 Coding School

**2018 - 2022** 

• Studying computer graphic, and make a small ray tracing rendering engine with C language, and small other games with unity.

## Associate Degree in web Development and Multimedia (Web Development)

**EWA School Agadir** 

**2013 - 2015** 

 Learning the basics of algorithms and problem solving, make websites with HTML/CSS and backend with php.

## Two Years in Faculty Option Physics (Physics)

Science Faculty IBN ZOHR (FSA)

**2011 - 2013** 

Two Years in Faculty Option Physics.

## Skills

Unity 3D • C#

HTML/CSS

Git

Blender

Adobe Photoshop

#### Achievement

# Speaker @ DevFest Agadir

GDG Agadir

Flutter Workshop.

# Participation @ Google for MENA Summit

Google

**12/2019** Dubai

 Summit for all Google Developers Leaders organised 100% by Google in Dubai.

# Participation @ AiHackTunisia

Google and InstaDeep

• 1st Intelligence Artificielle Hackathon organised by Google and InstaDeep in Tunisia.

#### 1337 Game Jam

1337

**1** 02/2019 Khouribga

• Game about Women's day theme.

#### **Portfolio**

- www.github.com/azertfx
- www.behance.net/azertfx
- m www.linkedin.com/in/abderrahimnabaoui

## Languages

Arabic Native English Intermediate French Intermediate